caraca look at this bro
AI caraca hand
on the 2nd attempt
I don't know if I told you
but for me to have used the shed
to do my face-to-face event that didn't work out
exchange it
I will do high post marketing
Anchieta we go on that
The Clouds in The
and today is the sixty-seven
Yeah
my first idea is to do it from there
continues
knows how
it's the first time i've been doing this and documenting
all here for you
I didn't even realize I was making the same mistake.
good thing you let me know in the comments
I was hesitating
and you are too much
but i think the deliverable connection
it's much bigger when we do it live
but i have 1 big problem here bro
this shed here has no internet
so I was thinking
how am i going to do this workshop then
caraca OR I spent it with salty
rent a chair and do something face-to-face
OR I do something interesting online
and then I have to pay room
1 lot of things
learn in the physical OR undertake in the digital
you will have equal risk
equal cost
is on
it's not as simple as I thought
the idea is to look for a magnificent Brunão
that i can stand
is on
exchanging ideas
like this with the camera
I can't do it here because of the internet
i wanted to see with you how much i go out to do a workshop
live
then it will be
Thursday
at 8 am
of the night
Thursday eight o'clock at night
changed took a while
ah Cayon
but I know
every hour is one thing
that's right bro
this here actually
it's not the end
it's the middle
haha